Sheet music collection on medical themes
Medical Historical Library, Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library
- Music advertising a product or practitioner, 4.
  - (Bile Bean Manufacturing Company) The Bile Bean March
    Composed by F. H. Fulford. London: The Bile Bean Manufacturing Company, ca. 1890. "Bile Beans for Biliousness."
  - (Bile Bean Manufacturing Company) Edward VII Grand Coronation March
    Composed by J. Michael Watson. London: The Bile Bean Manufacturing Company, ca. 1901. Edward VII became King of Great Britain in 1901.
  - (C. F. Blanke & Co.) Kofeko Two Step
    Composed by Albert A Stoll. St. Louis, Missouri: C. F. Blanke & Co., c. 1897. (Blanke's) Kofeko is a health beverage. Includes testimonials by physicians.
  - (C. F. Blanke & Co.) Village Boy Quick Step
    Composed by Robt. W. Edwards. St. Louis, Missouri: C. F. Blanke & Co., c. 1897. Advertises (Blanke's) Kofeko, a health beverage, and includes testimonials by physicians.
  - (C. V. Craft, Prescription Druggist) Blue Wings
    Words by Geo. W. Frey, music by Ed. H. Frey. Printed by Hatch Printing Co., Cleveland, Ohio. Compliments of C. V. Craft, Prescription Druggist, Flint, Michigan. Advertisement on back cover for Craft and three other companies in Flint, Michigan. Probably 19th cent.
  - (Perry Davis & Son) The "Pain Killer" Polka
    Composed by Frederic Archer. London: Cunningham Boosey & Sprague, n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). Full page advertisement for Perry Davis' Pain Killer on the back cover. Perry Davis & Son was based in Providence, R.I.
  - Doctor De Jongh
    May be missing cover. No information on creators or publisher. On how his sickly wife was cured by taking Dr. De Jongh's Cod Liver Oil.
  - (Dodd's Medicine Co.) America
    Buffalo, N.Y., Dodd's Medicine Co., n.d. (ca. 1910). The music is "My County 'Tis of Thee." The sheet advertises Dodd's Kidney Pills and includes testimonials, one dated 1910.
  - (Dood's Medicine Co.) America
    Another copy of the above.
  - (J. C. Eno, Inc.) Eno Sunshine
    Copyright 1947 by J. C. Eno, Inc., Bloomfield, N.J. Eno, an "effervescent salt," advertised on the back cover, is said to neutralize excess stomach acid and act as a speedy, gentle laxative. The song words advertise the product.
  - (Horace L. Fairchild, M.D,) 'Tis a Little Cotton Blossom
    Words and music by Dr. P. A. Shannon. Published by J. H. Morrison & Co., New Brunswick, N.J., n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). "Dr. P. A. Shannon's Great Plantation Melody." "As sung nightly by Dockstader's Minstrels." Advertisement on back cover for Dr. Dutton's Vegetable Discovery "a guaranteed cure for all blood diseases." Horace L. Fairchild, New Brunswick, N.J., is sole proprietor of this remedy.
  - (Forhan Company) That's the Song of Songs for Me: The Theme Song of the Forham Song Shop - Radio Feature
    Words by Henry Neely, music by Harold Levey. New York: Green & Stept Inc., c. 1929. Forhan's is a tooth paste advertised on the inside front cover and the back cover.
  - (Max Gessler) The Broken Wing
    Arranged by H. Bollman. Milwaukee, Wis.: Max Gessler, Ph. C., n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). Advertisement on back cover for Gessler's Magic Headache Wafers.
  - (Max Gessler) Robin Adair and Drink to Me Only With Thine Eyes
    Words to "Robin Adair" by Robert Burns. Words to "Drink to Me Only with Thine Eyes" by Ben Johnson. Milwaukee, Wis.: Max Gessler, Ph. C., n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). Advertisement for Gessler's Magic Headache Wafers on back cover.
  - (Dr. Greene Nervura Co.) Nervura Waltz
    Composed by Eugene C. Ramsdell. Copyright by Dr. Greene Nervura Co., Boston, ca. 1898. Nervura was sold as a "blood and nerve remedy" for the cure of a great many ailments. Advertisements on both front and back pages.
  - (Thomas Holloway) The Beautiful Prayer
    Words by Stanhope Gray, music by Lindsay Lennox. London: Thomas Holloway, n.d. (late 19th cent.). Advertisement on rear cover for Holloway's Pills and Ointment.
  - (Thomas Holloway) Sons of England, Raise Your Voices!
    Words and music by C. Preston Wynne. London: Thomas Holloway, 1902. Refers to the Coronation of King Edward VII. Advertises Holloway's pills and ointment.
  - (Keeley Institutes) Somebody, Somewhere, is Praying for You
    Words by George Cooper, music by Henry J. Sayers. New York: The Lyra Publishing Co. Copyright 1893 by Henry J. Sayers. A temperance song. Advertisement for "The Keeley Double-Chloride of Gold cure for nervous diseases, liquor and opium habits."
  - (Keeley Institutes) The Banner of Gold
    Words by Chas. E. Banks, music by Alonzo Hatch. Published by S. Brainard's Sons Co., Chicago. Copyright 1891 by Alonzo Hatch. "Respectfully dedicated to the Bi-Chloride of Gold Club." The words of the song directly advertise Bi-Chloride of Gold and refer to Dr. Keeley.
  - (Kerry, Watson & Co.) I Whistle and Wait for Katie
    Words and music by Michael Nolan, arranged by John S. Baker. Montreal: Kerry, Watson & Co., Wholesale Druggists, n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). Gray's Syrup of Red Spruce Gum was advertised for "all throat affections."
  - (Dr. Kilmer & Co.) Musica-Medicus
    Binghamton, N.Y.: Dr. Kilmer & Co., c. 1888. The lyrics advertise Dr. Kilmer's proprietary remedies including Swamp-Root, Ocean Weed, Consumption Oil, and Pills. On the reverse of the music is an article by Dr. Kilmer & Co.
  - (Koeing Medicine Co.) Say Dear Heart to Me
    Words and music by Arthur Eberlein. Chicago: Koenig Medicine Co., n.d. (early 20th cent.) Advertisments for Fumanoint, "for all cold troubles."
  - (Laboratoire d'Actino-Biologie) Ode au soleil
    Broadside. Words by E'Edd. Rostand, music by Dr. Garnaud. Advertsies "Algecrine" for pain, depression, and other ailments. "Produits J. Laurençon, Laboratoire d'Actino-Biologie, Villefranche (Rhône)." Early 20th century,
  - (Les Laboratoires Gobey) Le Legs
    Words by Philéas Lebesque, music by C.A. P. Ruysen. Paris: Laboratoires Gobey, n.d. [20th cent.]. Includes an insert addressed to physicians, offering the song, as the second in a series. The song, with a color image on the cover, is about the legacies of the singer's parents. The company produced Le Sirop Laxatif Gobey, Le Sirop Pectoral Gobey, and Le Sirop Sédatif Gobey.
  - (Dr. J. Lariviere Co.) Enduring Love
    Composed by Mme. Lillian Nordica. Boston: White-Smith Music Publishing Company, c. 1890. Cover advertises the Regulateur de Sante de la Femme du Dr. J. Lariviere, a remedy for women's ills. George Mortimer & Co., Inc., The Dr. J. Lariviere Co, proprietaires. There is a stamp on the music advertising John B. Beauvais, Inc., Prescription Pharmacists, Holyoke, Mass.
  - (A. H. Lewis Medicine Co.) Feel Like a Million
    Words and music by Will Waldron. St. Louis, Mo.: A. H. Lewis Medicine Co., c. 1928. Nature's Remedy, a "vegetable laxative and corrective," is advertised on the back cover.
  - (Dr. Lyons Tooth Powder) Manhattan Merry-Go-Round
    Words by Herman Pincus, music by Gustave Haenschen. New York: Joe Davis, Inc., Music Publishers, c. 1936. Theme song of Dr. Lyon's Tooth Powder Radio Program on WEAF.
  - (H. T. Mason Chemical Company) Tannhaueser March
    Composed by Richard Wagner. Philadelphia: H. T. Mason, Chemical Co., n.d. (late 19th cent.). Advertises a variety of products under the umbrella of "Mason's Health Defenders."
  - (Masters & Preston) Ginger Polka
    Composed by G.I.B. for Masters & Preston, Druggists and Pharmacists, Springfield, Mass. Dated ca. 1875. Advertises Pure Extract of Jamaica Ginger.
  - (Mattoni's Giesshübler) Ein G'spritzter mit Giess'
    Words by Beatrice Dovsky, music by Karl Kappeller. Vienna: Jos. Eberle & Co., n.d. (late 19th cent.). Song directly advertises the product.
  - (Dr. J. H. Maust, Surgeon-Dentist) The Flowers that Bloom in the Spring
    [By Gilbert and Sullivan] New York: Mendelssohn Publishing Co., n.d. (19th cent.) From the "Adelina Patti Series." J. H. Maust's dental practice in Pittsburgh is noted on the front page and is given a full page advertisement on the back cover.
  - (Medical Battery Company) The Lost Voice: A Refrain on Dr. Carter Moffat's Ammoniaphone
    Words by Percy G. Mocatta, music by Alfred Allen. London: The Medical Battery Company, Ltd., n.d. (late 19th cent.). Advertisement for Dr. Carter Moffat's Ammoniaphone Harness' Patent "for voice cultivation, and the cure of asthma, bronchitis, and all pulmonary affections. Dedicated to C. B. Harness, Esq."
  - (Moxie Nerve Food Co.) Just Make It Moxie For Mine
    Words by W. Pence Mitchell, music by Bert Potter. Boston: Moxie Nerve Food Co. of New England, c. 1904.
  - (The Munyon Homoeopathic Home Remedy Co.) Munyon's Liberty Song
    Words and music by J. M. Munyon. Published by M. D. Swisher, Philadelphia. Copyright by J. M. Munyon, n.d. (late 19th cent.). Back cover advertises Munyon's Inhaler and various Munyon "cures," for example, "Munyon's Kidney Cure." Munyon is referred to as Professor.
  - (The Munyon Homoeopathic Home Remedy Co.) The Nation's Song
    Words and music by J. M. Munyon. Published by M. D. Swisher, Philadelphia. Copyright by J. M. Munyon, n.d. (late 19th cent.). Back cover advertises Munyon's Inhaler and various Munyon "cures."
  - (The Munyon Homoeopathic Home Remedy Co.) The Nation's Song
    Words and music by J. M. Munyon. Published by M. D. Swisher, Philadelphia. Copyright by J. M. Munyon, n.d. (late 19th cent.). Testimonials to his remedies on back cover. Variant of previous item.
  - (The Munyon Homeopathic Home Remedy Co) The Nation's Song
    Another variant of the above two items.
  - (Munyon Remedy Company) Down Where the Paw-Paw Grows
    Words and music by J. M. Munyon. Presumably published by the Munyon Remedy Company, Philadelphia, n.d. (turn of the 20th cent.). Advertises Munyon's Paw Paw Tonic "for correcting indigestion, liver ailments and nervousness."
  - Munyon's Grand March
    Composed by Bart E. Grady. Boston: White-Smith Music Publishing Company, c. 1897. Shows the same image of Munyon as previous Munyon items, but does not include advertising.
  - (Murdock Liquid Food Co.) The Old Flag
    Words by Henry C. Bunner, music by Grant Drake. Boston: Murdock Liquid Food Co., 1898. Song "reprinted by permission for the Poem of H. C. Bunner, Copyright 1884, 1892 and 1896 by Charles Scribner's Sons." Testimonials on back page.
  - (New Mix Products) You've Got to Mix To-Day, so Mix the "New-Mix" Way
    Words and music by Jack Mahoney. New York: New-Mix Products, Inc., c. 1925. "Novelty Fox Trot." Advertises a toothpaste in the song and on the back cover.
  - (Oduntunder Dental Parlors) Odontunder Two-Step
    Composed by H. Wakefield Smith. Copyright 1898 by H. Wakefield Smith. "Published exclusively for the Odontunder Dental Parlors,...Cleveland, O." "We use Odontunder for painless extracting."
  - (Pastilles Géraudel) Chanson des belles promeneuses d'hiver
    Photocopy of a song, ca. 1907, advertising through its lyrics Pastilles Géraudel. The pastilles of M. Géraudel are advertised on the back cover as a remedy for coughing, bronchitis, laryngitis, etc.
  - (Plasmon, Limited) Humpty and Dumpty
    Words by Charles Wilmott, music by Hermann E. Darewski, Jr. Originally published by Francis, Day & Hunter, London, c. 1907. "Issued by Plasmon Limited, by arrangement with Messrs. Francis, Day & Hunter. Plasmon was a "milk albumin" health additive to mix into food or drink. It also manufactured products like cocoa with Plasmon already added. Advertisements on front and back covers.
  - (G. Réaubourg & Cie.) Dormeuse
    Words by Marceline Desbordes-Valmore, music by Marguerite Canal. Color image of a sleeping child. Lullaby with an advertisement for a sleeping aid, Passiflorine, manufactured by the Laboratoires de la Passiflorine, G. Réaubourg & Cie., Paris, n.d. [20th cent.]
  - (Schilling Corset Co.) A Golden Picture of Home
    Words and music by Barney Fagan. Chicago: The Chicago Music Co., c. 1885. This edition presumably published by the Schilling Corset Co., Detroit and Chicago. Corsets advertised include Dr. Schilling's Health Preserving Corset.
  - (Schilling Corset Co.) Swedish Wedding March
    Composed by Aug. Soderman. Presumably published by Schilling Corset Co., Detroit and Chicago, late 19th cent.
  - (A. A. Shafer) The Elderberry Rag
    Words by A. A. Shafer, music by Geo. F. Root (Tune - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp!) The song advertises A. A. Shafer's Pure Elderberry Wine, which possesses "diuretic and diaphoretic properties, an alterative, useful in rheumatism and other chronic diseases." "Made and guaranteed by A. A. Shafer, New Paltz, N.Y. Published after 1906 because reference is made to the Pure Food and Drug Act.
  - (I. Calvin Shafer) Grand March Militaire
    Composed by A. H. Kreutzberg. New York: Gage & Company, Publishers, c. 1876. Advertisement on back for "L. Calvin Shafer, successor to P. Gordon, manufacturer of pure fruit syrups, juices, cordials, bitters & c.," New York. Presented with the compliments of Wm. R. Laird, Druggist, Jersey City, N.J.
  - (I. Calvin Shafer) Grand March Militaire
    Composed by A. H. Kreutzberg. New York: Gage & Company, Publishers, c. 1876. Back cover advertises "I. Calvin Shafer, successor to P. Gordon, manufacturer of pure fruit syrups, juices, cordials, bitters & c." Presented with the compliments of Vincent's Open-All-Night Pharmacy, Brooklyn, New York.
  - (Sherrouse Medicine Co, Ltd.) Dr. Tichenor's Antiseptic Waltz
    Composed by Louis Blake. New Orleans: Sherrouse Medicine Co., Ltd., n.d. (late 19th cent.). The antiseptic is for internal and external use.
  - (Silsbee's Podogague) Podogogue Lyrics No. 4
    No information on creator. Cincinnati: John Church, Jr., c. 1866. On Silsbee's Podogogue, a patent medicine.
  - (Société Générale d'Eaux Minérales Naturelles du Bassin de Vichy) Vichy-purgatif: Grand galop brillant
    Composed by Mademoiselle G. R. Advertises Eau Purgatif de Vichy.
  - (Southington Medicine Co.) The Johnstown Disaster
    Composed by George B. Richards. Copyright by George B. Richards, 1889. "Proprietors of Dr. Hart's King of All Remedies, the Great Blood Purifier..." No information on the location of the Southington Medicine Co.
  - (I. Strouse & Co.) A New Polish Dance
    Composed by Frederic Brandeis. Copyright 1888 by R.A. Saalfield. Published exclusively for I. Strouse & Co., New Haven, Conn., Manufacturers of Dr. Scott's Electric Corsets. Illustrated advertisement on back cover.
  - (Thacher Medicine Co.) Dixie's Land
    By Dan. D. Emmett, arranged by F.M. Chatanooga, Tenn.: Thacher Medicine Co., n.d. [19th cent.]. Familiar "I wish I was in the land of cotton.." Back cover advertises Dr. Thacher's Liver and Blood Syrup.
  - (Dr. Thomson Medicine Co.) Dr. Thomson's Triumphal March
    Composed by Walter W. Gillman. Calaise, Maine: The Dr. Thomson Medicine Co., n.d. (turn of 20th cent.). Advertisements for Dr. Thomson's Compound Extract of Sarsaparilla and for Dr. Thompson's Dyspepsia. Dr. Robert Thomson was a graduate of Bellevue Hospital Medical College and served as a surgeon in the Civil War.
  - (W. H. Veno, M.D.) When Great Veno Came!
    Words and music by Stephe [sic] S. Bonbright. Cincinnati: Home Music Company, c. 1895. "Written expressly for the world-renowned specialist, W. H. Veno, M.D."
  - (E. S. Wells) Song and Chorus of Rough On Rats
    Music by Jules Juniper. Jersey City, N.J.: E. S. Wells, c. 1882. In addition to Rough on Rats, which kills rats, there are advertisements for a variety of other Wells remedies.
  - (A. R. White, M.D.) Mother's Wandering Boy: Temperance Song and Chorus
    Music by Thomas Belcher. Presumably published by A. R. White, Indianapolis, ca. 1889. Advertises Dr. White's Pulmonaria and Dr. White's Compound Dandelion Alterative.
  - (A. R. White, M.D.) What O'Clock?
    Music by Thomas Belcher. Indianapolis: A. R. White, M.D., c. 1888. Includes testimonials.
  - (Willard White Company) Melorose March and Two-Step
    Composed by Marion W. Rose. Published by Willard White Co., Chicago. Copyright 1910 by A. E. Miller. "Melorose preparations" are cosmetics including "beauty cream," face powder, and rouge.
  - (Willard White Company) In Beauty-Land
    Words and Music by H. Wakefield Smith. Chicago: Willard White Co., c. 1914. The song directly advertises Melorose cream, powder, and rouge. Testimonials on the back cover
  - (Willard White Company) The Song of the Melorose Waltz
    Words by Adelebert E. Miller, music by F. Henri Klickmann. Chicago: Willard White Company, c. 1913. Melorose is incorporated into the song. Testimonials on back cover.
  - The "Wincarnis" Waltz
    "Specially composed for the Proprietors of 'Wincarnis' by James M. Glover, Director of Music, Drury Lane Theatre, London, W.C." No copyright date (turn of 20th cent.). "Wincarnis," sold at wine merchants, grocers, and chemists (pharmacies), "has an immediate stimulating and recuperative effect."
  - (W. Woodward Ltd.) The Woodward Lullaby La-loo, La-loo
    Words by Rose Fyleman, music by Will Grosz. London: W. Woodward, Ltd., c. 1935. Advertisement on the back cover for "Gripe Water" for babies.
  - (The Zam-Buk Company) The Zam-Buk Grand March
    No information on composer. Published by C. E. Fulford, Ltd., n.d. (turn of 20th cent). The Zam-Buk Company is located in Leeds, England. Zam-Buk is advertised as the "Great Skin-Cure and First-Aid Healing Balm."
  - (The Zam-Buk Company) Zam-Buk Grand March
    Another copy of the previous item.
  - (The Zinn's Health Store) "Our Martha": In Blossom Time
    By Henry J. Zinn. Newark, N.J.: The Zinn's Health Store, c. 1947. "Our Martha" appears to refer to Richer Blossom Honey sold by the store.
- Bromo-Seltzer sheet music, 5.
  The Emerson Drug Company, Baltimore, Maryland, first produced Bromo-Seltzer in 1888. It was marketed as a remedy for headache and neuralgia, and also for insomnia, nervousness, hangover or depression following alcoholic excess, nervous dyspepsia, and stomach disorders. Early advertisements noted that it contained no cocaine and no morphine.
  From the 1890s to the 1910s, the company produced collections of popular sheet music with piano and organ accompaniment. Many of the songs were sentimental or patriotic. The front and back covers of the music contained advertisements for Bromo-Seltzer. The music was distributed for free by druggists all over the United States, many of whose names are stamped on the cover page of the music, or the pieces could be obtained from the Music Department of the Emerson Drug Company by enclosing a stamp and a Bromo-Seltzer wrapper.
  Most items do not have copyright dates. The most recent copyright date is 1900. A number of pieces are by Philadelphia composer George M. Vickers or copyrighted by Vickers.
  There are several series:
  (1) Individual titles, not part of a collection. For one of these, "Murphy's Head," the words of the song directly advertised Bromo-Seltzer as a remedy for hangovers. These appear to date from 1890 to 1892.
  (2) Emerson Drug Co., The Bromo-Seltzer Collection of 54 Popular Songs, Complete and Unabridged. Full music Size with Piano and Organ Accompaniment. The cover image is of a woman playing a Chickering piano. This edition predates the next and the song sheets date from 1890-1892.
  (3) Emerson Drug Co., The Bromo-Seltzer Collection of 74 Popular Songs, Complete and Unabridged, Full Music Size with Piano and Organ Accompaniment. Some songs include testimonials from 1892 and others have testimonials from 1895. A few have "New Selections, Added January 1st 1898. A very few mention the forthcoming Columbian Exposition of 1893. The date range is therefore ca. 1892-1898. The cover image is of a woman playing a Stieff Piano.
  (4) Emerson Drug Co., The Bromo-Seltzer Collection of 83 Popular Songs, Complete & Unabridged with Piano & Organ Accompaniment. Version 1, with red and blue print, lists "New Selections Added, January 1st, 1899." These songs may have a page of testimonials dated 1895. The second version, black and white, which should be slightly later, lists the same songs as "New Selections Added." The date is ca. 1899.
  (5) Emerson Drug. Co., Bromo-Seltzer Edition of 171 Popular Selections, Complete and Unabridged with Piano & Organ Accompaniment. There are two versions. Version 1 shows a woman blowing a horn with her arm around a giant Bromo-Seltzer bottle. Version 2 has a decorative design that incorporates musical instruments and sheet music. These editions of 171 selections are more recent than the previous 83 popular songs and from the images are likely to date between 1900 and 1910.
  (6) Emerson Drug Co., The Bromo-Seltzer New Edition: 52 Popular Selections, Complete & Unabridged with Piano & Organ Accompaniment. This edition presumes that there is a complete list of 171 selections. It is also likely to date from 1900 to 1910.
  (7) "Edition De Luxe." These have cover pages in color and were copyrighted by Will Wood. The De Luxe Music Co., New York, was the sole selling agent. None are dated. This sheet music no longer advertised Bromo-Seltzer on the front cover nor had the names of pharmacies printed on them. They were distributed "Compliments of Emerson Drug. Co." Advertisements appear on the bottom of pages of music and on the back cover. They date from ca. 1910. De Luxe Music Co. probably made similar arrangements to print music with advertisements for other companies.
  - Bromo-Seltzer Album, Containing 38 Songs and 12 Instrumental Pieces, ca. 1895 (Box 12)
    Baltimore: Emerson Drug Co., n.d. (ca. 1895).
  - Adelaide: Polka Mazurka (171 popular selections, version 1), ca. 1900-1910
  - Adelaide: Polka Mazurka (171 popular selections, version 2), ca. 1900-1910
  - Adelaide: Polka Mazurka (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Adelaide: Polka Mazurka (83 popular songs, version 2), ca. 1899
  - Afterwards (171 popular selections, version 2), ca. 1900-1910
  - Alice, Where Art Thou? (74 popular songs), ca. 1895
  - Alice, Where Art Thou? (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - All's Right (52 popular selections), ca. 1900-1910
  - All's Right (171 popular selections, version 1), ca. 1900-1910
  - All's Right (171 popular selections, version 2), ca. 1900-1910
  - America (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - America (83 popular songs, version 2), ca. 1899
  - American's Farewell (52 popular selections), c. 1896, pub. ca. 1900-1910
  - American's Farewell (171 popular selections, version 1), c. 1896, pub. ca. 1900-1910
  - Annie Laurie (171 popular selections, version 1), ca. 1900-1910
  - Annie Laurie (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Apple Blossom March (171 popular songs, version 1), c. 1886, pub. ca. 1900-1910
  - Apple Blossom March (171 popular songs, version 2), c. 1886, pub. ca. 1900-1910
  - The Arrow Dance (83 popular songs, version 1), c. 1894, pub. ca. 1899
  - At the Gate (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Auld Lang Syne (54 popular songs), ca. 1890-1892
  - Auld Lang Syne (171 popular songs, version 2), ca. 1900-1910
  - Auld Lang Syne (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Il Bacio Waltz (The Kiss) (83 popular songs, version 2), ca. 1899
  - Barney, Oh, Why Must You Leave Me? (52 popular selections), ca. 1900-1910
  - Beautiful Moonlight (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms (Edition DeLuxe), ca. 1910
  - Belle of Cuba Quickstep (83 popular songs, version 1), c. 1895, pub. ca. 1899
  - Ben Bolt (171 popular selections, version 1), ca. 1900-1910
  - Ben Bolt (74 popular songs), ca. 1895
  - Ben Bolt (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899
  - Ben Bolt (83 popular songs, version 2), ca. 1899
  - The Black Key Polka Mazourka (171 popular selections, version 1), ca. 1900-1910
  - The Black Key Polka Mazourka (171 popular selections, version 2), ca. 1900-1910
  - The Black Key Polka Mazourka (83 popular songs, version 1), ca. 1899